Guide to the Ezra Stoller Photographs of the Art and Architecture Building, Yale University
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Ezra Stoller photographs of the Art and Architecture Building, Yale University
1963-2005
RU 869
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.25
The materials consists of black and white photographs of the Yale Art and Architecture Building shortly after its completion in 1963. Also includes a commemorative United States Postal Service stamp made from Ezra Stoller's photograph.
Stoller, Ezra
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 46-B (YRG 46-B), Records and materials documenting individual Yale buildings, facilities, and grounds.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by topic.
Scope and Contents
The materials consists of black and white photographs of the Yale Art and Architecture Building shortly after its completion in 1963. Also includes a commemorative United States Postal Service stamp made from Ezra Stoller's photograph.
College buildings; Commemorative postage stamps; Photographs; Stoller, Ezra; Yale University -- Pictorial works; Yale University -- Buildings
- Photographs of the Art and Architecture Building by Ezra Stoller, circa 1963; Accession 2000-A-043
  - Architectural Studios w/ Minerva [30x38 mounted] (Box 1)
  - Chapel Street Façade from South [30x38 mounted] (Box 2)
  - Chapel Street Façade from South East [30x38 mounted] (Box 3)
  - Gallery [30x38 mounted] (Box 4)
  - View from the South East [30x38 mounted] (Box 5)
  - 2nd Floor Main Gallery [30x38 mounted] (Box 6)
  - Student Lounge [16x20] (Box 7)
  - 2nd Floor Main Gallery [16x20] (Box 7)
  - Gallery look at Library [16x20] (Box 7)
  - Architectural Studio w/ Minerva [16x20] (Box 7)
  - Lounge w/ view down Chapel Street [16x20] (Box 7)
  - Sculpture Court [16x20] (Box 7)
  - York Street Façade [16x20] (Box 7)
  - View from the South East [16x20] (Box 7)
  - Stairwell [16x20] (Box 7)
  - Chapel Street Façade from South [16x20] (Box 7)
  - Chapel Street Façade [16x20] (Box 7)
  - Ground Level Entrance [16x20] (Box 7)
  - View from East YUAG at left [16x20] (Box 7)
  - U-Channel Bridge [16x20] (Box 7)
  - Architectural Studios w/ Minerva [16x20] (Box 7)
  - Penthouse w/ Menorah [16x20] (Box 7)
  - Library [16x20] (Box 7)
  - Sculpture Garden [16x20] (Box 7)
  - Penthouse w/ Menorah [16x20] (Box 7)
- Commemorative USPS Stamp of the Art & Architecture Building based on Ezra Stoller photograph, 2005; Accession 2006-A-123
  - Commemorative stamp, 2005 (Box 1)
- Photographs of the Art and Architecture building, Yale University, by Ezra Stoller, circa 1963; Accession 2007-A-100
  - View from the South East [169 Y 1], circa 1963 (Box 1)
  - Chapel Street Façade from South East [169 Y 13], circa 1963 (Box 1)
  - Gallery Look at Library [169 Y 16], circa 1963 (Box 1)
  - 2nd Floor Main Gallery? [169 Y 20], circa 1963 (Box 1)
  - Architectural Studio w/ Minerva [169 Y 22], circa 1963 (Box 1)